"use strict";var hpQuiz=[{question:"What was the spell Snape used on the whomping willow?",options:["Impedimenta","Fidelius","Immobulus","Reducio"],answer:2,isAnswered:!1},{question:"What is kissing called?",options:["Frenching","Snogging","Slugging","Snubbing"],answer:1,isAnswered:!1},{question:"What is the name of Draco Malfoy's son?",options:["Scorpius","Lucius","Diego","Severus","Dane"],answer:0,isAnswered:!1},{question:"What creature does Dumbledore have as a pet?",options:["Efreet","Fey","Troll","Phoenix","Basilisk"],answer:3,isAnswered:!1},{question:"What is Voldemort's final horcrux?",options:["A mirror","A snake","A brooch","Harry Potter"],answer:1,isAnswered:!1},{question:"Who takes over as headmaster of Hogwarts after Dumbledore's death?",options:["Narcissa Black","Professor Trelawny","Delores Umbridge","Professor Snape"],answer:3,isAnswered:!1},{question:"Who killed Deatheater Antonin Dolohov during the Battle of Hogwarts?",options:["Professor Flitwick","Ron Weasley","Falling Debris","Hermione Granger"],answer:0,isAnswered:!1},{question:"Who was the old Care of Magical Creatures teacher?",options:["Professer Kettleburn","Professor Hagrid","Professor Lupin","Professor Grubbly-Plank"],answer:0,isAnswered:!1},{question:"How much does a twelve-week course of Apparition lessons cost?",options:["17 Galleons","12 Galleons","3 Galleons","Nothing - It's Free"],answer:1,isAnswered:!1},{question:"How much gold do the Weasleys win in the annual Daily Prophet Grand Prize Galleon Draw?",options:["800 Galleons","7k Galleons","700 Galleons","700 Sickles"],answer:2,isAnswered:!1},{question:"Where do Harry's aunt and uncle live?",options:["Little Hangleton","Hogsmeade","Little Whinging","Godric's Hollow"],answer:2,isAnswered:!1},{question:"How many times do Fred and George's fireworks multiply by if you try to vanish them?",options:["25","20","10","15"],answer:2,isAnswered:!1},{question:"How many times was Nearly Headless Nick hit in the neck with a blunt axe?",options:["47","45","20","25"],answer:1,isAnswered:!1},{question:"What do Ron and Hermione use to destroy Helga Hufflepuff's cup?",options:["A basilisk Fang","Fiendfyre","Sword of Gryffindor","Patronum Charm"],answer:0,isAnswered:!1},{question:"What is Dumbledore's full name?",options:["Albus Percival Brian Wulfric Dumbledore","Albus Wulfric Brian Percival Dumbledore","Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore"],answer:2,isAnswered:!1},{question:"What does O.W.L. stand for?",options:["Offical Wizarding License","Organised Wizard Learning","Ordinary Wizarding Level","Outstanding Wizard Lesson"],answer:2,isAnswered:!1}];
